Yes, it's been a while.
はい、久々
Yes, it's been a long time.
はい、めっちゃ久々
It's been a really long time.
めちゃくちゃ久々
hey.
ね
Akane-chan?
あかねちゃん?
Is it happening?
なってる?
Did it go well?
ちゃんとなった?
It became.
なった
Are you no longer a minor?
未成年じゃなくなった?
Yeah.
うん
Did you turn 18?
ちゃんと18歳になった?
I turned 18 years old.
18歳になった
It's been a while.
久々だね
How much is it for the third time?
3回目ましてくらい?
It's about the 3rd or 4th time, right?
3、4回目ましてくらいだよね?
I agree.
そうだね
That's right.
そうだよね
No, it won't change.
いや、変わんないね
But it's great that you've been able to keep in touch with your uncle.
だけどちゃんとおじさんと連絡通り続けてて偉いです
Yeah.
うん
Too cute.
可愛すぎ
Hey, you just turned 18, right?
え、18歳になったばっかりでしょ?
yes.
そう
It really just happened the other day.
もう本当にこないだになったばっかりでね
Yeah.
うん
That's why it's great that you keep in touch.
それでちゃんと連絡してくるのがちゃんと偉い
Really.
本当に
Akane-chan.
あかねちゃん
So, let me introduce myself again. How old are you now?
じゃあ 改めて自己紹介だけど、今お幾歳ですか?
I'm 18 years old now.
今は18歳
18 years old.
18歳
Yes, what's your name?
はい、お名前は?
This is Akane.
あかねです
Akane-chan.
あかねちゃん
Akane-chan is 18 years old, what is she doing now?
あかねちゃん18歳で、今何?
What are you doing?
何してる?
high school student?
高校生?
Have you quit high school yet?
高校生もうやめた?
Yes, I finished high school.
うん、高校終わった
Is it finished?
終わった?
Yeah.
うん
It's cold.
寒いね
cold.
寒い
18 years old.
18歳
It's over.
終わった
終 わ った
I see, what are you doing now?
そっか、今何してんの?
I'm not doing anything right now.
今は何もしてない
Are you not doing anything?
何もしてない?
Already NEET?
もうニート?
neat.
ニート
Nice, looks like you're 18 years old.
いいね、18歳っぽくていいね
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
ねえ
Are you hungry?
お腹減ったでしょ?
I'm hungry.
お腹減った
Hey.
ねえ
It's about the third time I've met my uncle,
おじさんと3回目ましてぐらいだけど、
All the food was delicious, right?
全部ご飯おいしかったでしょ?
It was delicious.
おいしかった
Hey.
ねえ
It's too cute though.
可愛すぎなんだけど
Peace.
ピ ースして
cute.
可愛い
18 years old.
18歳
Stay like this, stay like this.
こんな、こんないでよって
Please stop doing that.
そんなやめてよって
Did you get a boyfriend?
彼氏はできた?
I haven't had a boyfriend.
彼氏できてない
Haven't you done it?
できてない?
Yeah.
うん
So, do you feel like your ex-boyfriend?
じゃああの、前の元彼のまんまって感じ?
yes.
そう
He's your ex-boyfriend, are you still together?
元彼で、まだあってんの?
With my ex-boyfriend.
元彼と
Is it not there anymore?
もうあってない?
It doesn't exist anymore.
もうあってない
It doesn't exist anymore?
もうあってないんだ?
Yeah.
うん
So what, you broke up with your ex-boyfriend?
じゃあ何、元彼からそれ分かれて、
It's still new, hasn't it been done yet?
まだ新しい、できてないんだ?
yes.
そう
why?
なんで?
Encounters are a mess, aren't they?
出会いめちゃめちゃあるでしょ?
That's it.
って
No, that's not true.
いや、そんなことない
Doesn't that happen?
そんなことあるでしょ?
18 years old.
18歳
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is that so?
そうなのか
copper?
どう?
It's cold like this, but don't you miss human skin?
こんな寒いけどさ、人肌恋しいじゃん?
Don't you think you want a boyfriend?
彼氏欲しいなって思わないの?
want.
欲しい
You want it, right?
欲しいよね?
Yeah.
うん
I want it, but I just can't do it.
欲しいけど、やっぱりできないんだ、
That's what it is.
そういうのは
I see.
そっか
Akane-chan is cute, isn't she?
アカネちゃん、可愛いのにね、なんかね
I'm getting really into it, but...
うちさん、ドハマりしてるんだけど、
18 years old.
18歳
Yeah.
うん
What do women like?
女性何が好きなの?
What do you usually do?
普段何すんの?
I'm 18 years old and don't like anything.
18歳、何も好きじゃない
18 years old, don't you like anything?
18歳、何も好きじゃないの?
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そっかそっか
What are you doing at home?
おうちで何すんの?
I'm sleeping at home.
おうちで寝てる
Are you sleeping at home?
おうちで寝てんの?
Yeah.
うん
It's cold.
寒いな
Are you going to a hotel?
ホテル行く?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
This is my first time going to a hotel with my wife.
ホテルさ、おうちさんとさ、行くのは初めてじゃん
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever been to a love hotel?
ラブホとかってさ、行ったことあんの?
I've never been there.
行ったことない
Have you never been?
行ったことないの?
Yeah.
うん
It's a love hotel debut, right?
ラブホデビューってことでしょ?
yes.
そう
That's right.
そうだよね
After all, including my ex-boyfriend, they're all the same age, right?
だって元彼とかもさ、全員同い年とかでしょ?
yes.
そう
One of them all.
全員つかその一人
Yeah.
うん
I'm not going to a love hotel.
行かないよね、ラブホ
I've never been there.
行ったことない
I can't go.
行 けないよね
Yeah.
うん
I know a lot of good hotels,
おうちさん、いっぱいいいホテル知ってるから、
I'll do good things for you with my life experiences.
いっぱい人生経験でいいことしてあげるね
I'll tell you a lot.
教えてあげるね、いっぱい
By the way, when did Akane-chan start junior high school?
ちなみにさ、あかねちゃんはさ、初中いつだったの?
When I was in high school.
高校生のとき
When you were in high school?
高校生のとき?
Yeah.
うん
Well, just recently, I was a high school student.
だ ってついこの間じゃん、高校生って
How old were you here?
ここ何年生のときだった?
2nd year high school student.
高校2年生
So around 17, 16 years old.
じゃあ17歳、16歳くらい
Really like a year ago?
ほ んと1年前とか?
Yeah.
うん
What, did you abandon the girl at that time too?
え、そのときに少女も捨てたの?
yes.
そう
Yeah.
えぇ
How many people have experience?
経験人数は?
1 person.
1人
So it's just that person?
じゃあもうその人だけ?
yes.
そう
That's right.
そうなんだ
One person with experience?
経験人数1人の人?
yes.
そう
It's so tight.
ピチピチだよ
Aren't you going to university?
大学は行かないの?
I won't go.
行かない
Aren't you going?
行かないんだ?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's go to the hotel.
じゃあもう行こうか、ホテル
Hey, don't you want to eat?
ちょっとさ、ご飯も食べたくない?
i want to eat.
食べたい
Are you hungry?
お腹減ったよね?
How about a hotel?
ホテルでどう?
Something like rice.
ご飯とか
Yeah.
うん
You've never had it before, right? Eating at a hotel.
食 ったことないでしょ、ホテルでご飯
do not have.
ない
No, right?
ないでしょ
Eating at a love hotel.
ラブホでご飯とか
Yeah.
うん
I thought I'd go for a while.
ちょっと行こうかなって
Yeah.
うん
Yahoo.
やっほー
What about a love hotel?
なんかさ、どうラブホ?
this.
これ
first time.
初めて
It’s your first time, right?
初めてでしょ?
Well, the front desk was there.
てかさ、フロントいたじゃん
It was stopped.
止められたじゃん
Are you a junior high school student?
中学生になってますか?
Like, at the reception.
みたいなさ、受付でさ
My uncle was a little surprised.
ちょっとおじさんびっくりしたわ
Well, you submitted your ID.
ちゃんとさ、身分証提出したじゃん
So it's okay, I guess.
じゃあ大丈夫なんですね、みたいなさ、
It was okay.
大丈夫だったじゃん
I guess it can be stopped.
やっぱ止められるんだね
Just like this.
こうやってちょっと
Is it true?
本当になってますか?
Something like that.
みたいなさ
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
I was surprised.
びっくりした
It's my first love hotel, and I don't have to submit ID like that.
初ラブホがさ、そんな身分証提出なんてさ、
I wonder what that means.
どういうことってなるやんね
It will be.
なる
After all, it's your first love hotel.
だってガチで初ラブホでしょ
Was your uncle surprised too?
おじさんもびっくりした?
I haven't been asked for much.
あんまり求められたことなくて
ID card.
身分証
So what is this?
そんで、これ何でしょ?
Did you eat Jagariko?
じゃがりこ食べたの?
Jagariko.
じゃがりこ
I'm hungry.
お腹すきなんだ
I came here to eat.
ご飯食べに来たじゃん
I'm hungry.
お腹減ったって
How about food at the hotel?
ホテルでご飯どう?
If you say that.
って言ったら
Relaxed?
のぶしい?
Are you nervous at the hotel?
ホテル緊張すんの?
get nervous?
緊張する?
It's cute.
かわいいね
I was nervous when I entered the hotel.
緊張すんのやったり、ホテル入ると
Can I have some?
ちょっと持ってとる?
Now 18.
今18
Dad.
パパ
If someone tells me that my dad is 18, I won't be able to digress.
パパ18って言われたら余談しちゃいけなっちゃうよ
How old is your dad?
パパいくつ?
Daddy 38.
パパ38
Daddy 38?
パパ38?
Yeah.
うん
Daddy 38?
パパ38?
yes.
そう
Look at this.
これ見るね
You can still see Dad.
パパまだ全然見えますよね
Is your dad 38?
パパ38なの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I see.
そっか
That's right.
そうだよね
That one from 07 or 08?
07とか08とかのあれ?
yes.
そう
Is your mom around the same age?
ママも同じ歳くらい?
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
Look at this.
これ見るね
Mom and dad, are you okay?
パパ、ママ大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Mom and Dad, do you know?
パパ、ママ知ってんの?
You don't know.
知らないよね
i don't know.
知らない
What if I find out?
バレたらどうすんの?
I'll apologize if I find out.
バレたら謝る
Do you think there is no apology?
謝 ら ないと思ってる?
Yes, I apologize.
うん、謝る
apologize?
謝る?
Shall I apologize?
謝っちゃう?
How do you apologize?
なんて謝るの?
I'm sorry.
ごめんねって
It's cute, but it's serious.
かわいいんだけどマジで
Dad, are you watching mom?
パパ、ママ見てるかな?
Dad.
パパ
Dad, are you watching mom?
パパ、ママ見てるかな?
18 years old.
18歳
I'm going to enjoy some delicious food now.
今からちょっと美味しく召し上がらせていただきますけど
Yeah.
うん
You've only ever been naughty with one of them, right?
エッチなことはさ、今までさ、その1人とかでしょ?
Do you like it?
好 きなの?
like.
好き
Akane-chan.
アカネちゃん
Don't you like it?
好きない?
What do you like?
どういうのが好きなの?
Do you like penis?
おちんちん好き?
like.
好き
lie?
嘘?
You've only had one bottle, right?
1本しか飲めたことないでしょ?
still.
まだ
You've only experienced one, right?
1本しか経験ないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
What kind of penis was that?
そのおちんちんはどういうおちんちんだったの?
Long and thin.
細長い
Did your penis become long and thin?
細長いおちんちになったの?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
So, you only have experience with elongated penises?
じゃあ、細長いちんこしかまだ経験がないってこと?
This is 18 years old.
これ が18歳だよ
So, do you like it?
で、好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
You said Onayushi, right?
おなゆしって言ったよね?
That's your ex-boyfriend, right?
あの元彼だよね?
That person you showed me the photo of before...
前に写真見せてくれたあの...
yes.
そう
He's a bit handsome, isn't he?
ちょっとイケメンだよね?
Handsome.
イケメン
He's a bit young and handsome.
ちょっと若くてイケメンだね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Ah, then the only thing you know about that person is sex.
あ、じゃあその人との、そのことのセクスしかまだ知らないって
Isn't that so?
こと だよね?
Welcome to the world of adults.
大 人の世界へようこそ
Welcome to the world.
ワールドへようこそ
I'll tell you all about it.
いっぱいじゃあ教えてあげますからね
Eh, then it's been a while since we've seen each other face to face, right?
え、じゃあちんこも対面、全然久しぶりってことになるよね?
yes.
そう
Today is special, amazing, 18 years old.
今日はさ、特別さ、すごいさ、18歳、
If I tell you that there's a new girl,
ありたての女の子がいるって言ったらさ、
Please come visit my uncle a lot.
いっぱいおじさんのところに来てさ、
Even among all of this, I will carefully select them and have them represent my penis.
そんな中でも厳選して、おちんちん代表してもらうから
I prepared my penis.
おちんちん用意したから
Look here.
ほら見て
It's penis-to-chin though.
おちんちん対面ですけど
What do you think?
どうですか?
penis.
おちんちん
It’s been a while.
久々の
Long time no see.
久々
Long time no see?
久々?
Yeah.
うん
How about this?
これどう?
Look, at first glance, this is the second one, right?
見てさ、パッと見、これ2本目でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Good, finally, finally.
いいよいいよいいよ
This is your second one, right?
これ2本目でしょ?
Yeah.
うん
How about the second one?
2本目どう?
Take a quick look, take a quick look, which one looks bigger, your ex-boyfriend's dick or yours?
パッと見さ、パッと見さ、元彼さんのちんことどっちがでかそう?
This way.
こっち
Does this one look big?
こっちがでかそう?
Yeah.
うん
Does it look long and thin?
細長そう?
It suddenly seems long.
ふと長そう
Does it seem long?
ふと長そう?
By the way, have you ever seen that video?
ふと長いのはさ、ちなみにさ、その映像とかでも見たことあるの?
be.
ある
There is.
あるんだ
What, do you usually watch erotic videos?
え、普段エロ動画とかは?
look.
見る
look?
見る?
Yeah.
うん
Seriously, you're so honest.
ほんとにじゃあもうほんと素直だね、
Don't lie.
嘘つかないで
Does it seem long?
ふと長そう?
Yeah.
うん
I wonder which one is the answer.
答えどっちなんだろうね
Well, let's try it out first.
じゃあまず、触ってみようか
It was the smell, something like that.
匂いだったりさ、なんか
It's kind of perverted to touch me.
触ること変態だね、なんか
different.
違う
Oh, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
え、わかんないわかんないわかんない
It's an 18 year old bill.
18歳札さんだね
How about Kane-chan?
かねちゃんどう?
What does the answer look like?
答えはどうっぽい?
Suddenly it's long.
ふと長い
Is it suddenly long?
ふと長い?
Yeah.
うん
Is it suddenly long?
ふと長いか
The answer seems long.
答えふと長いね
By the way, how about your dog?
ちょっとじゃあ、お犬の方はどうですか?
Does your dog smell a little naughty?
お犬の方はちょっとエッチな匂いします?
Yes, I will.
うん、する
do?
する?
Really?
ほんとに?
Yeah.
うん
Does it smell a little sweaty?
ちょっと汗臭い?
Yeah.
うん
yes.
そう
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめんごめんごめん
Oh, sorry, sorry.
あ、ごめんごめん
I stumbled a bit and took a look.
ちょっと足がつまずい、ちょっと見て
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめんごめん
Just leave it alone, wait a minute, then...
そのままさ、ちょっとさ、じゃあさ、
Shall we check the answers?
答え合わせしてみる?
I suddenly wondered if it was long or something different.
ふと長いか、それとも違うのかって
Who should decide the answer to this?
これ、答えって誰が決めていいのかな?
Suddenly, suddenly?
ふと、ふといか?
Isn't it random?
ふとくない?
What do you mean by "skinny" or "slim"?
ふといか、細いかっていうのは?
I.
私
I?
私?
Is it okay for Akane-chan to decide after all?
やっぱアカネちゃん判断でいい?
What if this is wrong?
これ、違ってたらどうしよう?
No, suddenly.
いや、ふとくなか
What should I do?
どうする?
this.
これ
Can I make a mess?
ぐちゃぐちゃにしていい?
Okay.
いいよ
Can I say high speed?
高速とかしていい?
Okay.
いいよ
Oh, take it off yourself?
あ、自分で脱げと?
Should I take it off myself?
自分で脱げと?
That's some kind of reaction.
なんか反応があれですね
What's your reaction?
どうですか反応?
This is suddenly long.
これは、ふと長い
It's suddenly long.
ふと長いんだ
This is suddenly long.
これふと長いんだ
This is quite long.
これふと長い
So, that means you're correct.
じゃあ、正解っていうことですね
correct answer.
正解
Ah, that's correct.
あ、正解なんだね
I see.
なるほど
What do you think of the raw dick you see in the video and the one you see in Magica?
映像で見るのと、マジカで見る生チンコはどうです?
The impact is different.
迫力が違う
Is it more impressive?
迫力違う?
yes.
そう
Well then, once again.
じゃあ、改めて
I'm at home, can I have a look?
自家でじゃあ、ちょっと触ってもらっていい?
You touch it with a cute face.
可愛い顔して触るんだね
You don't have to touch it properly either.
触り方もきっこちなくていいね
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Do you hate it?
嫌がっちゃうの?
That's it.
そんな
Try a little peroncho.
ちょっとペロンチョしてみて
That's a pervert.
変態だね
Well then, it seems long.
じゃあ、ふと長い
It's small.
小さいね
Yeah.
うん
It feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Do you have tissues?
ティッシュいる?
Yeah.
うん
Press a tissue?
ティッシュ押す?
Were you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張隠れた?
Yeah.
うん
Did you hide a little?
ちょっとだけ隠れた?
Were you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張隠れた?
Yeah.
うん
After all, it's important to greet people properly.
やっぱね、ちゃんと挨拶することが大事だよね
Use your dick.
チンコ使ってね
Let's enjoy the experience.
体感堪能しようかな
Are you sure?
よろしい?
Yeah.
うん
Even if I'm told no, I'll do it.
ダメって言われてもやっちゃうんだけどね、
That's it.
そんなのは
That's a cute outfit.
かわいい服だね
Do you like customers?
お客さん好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
I don't know though.
わかんないけど
I wonder if Akane-chan knows the word raw liver body?
アカネちゃんは生肝体って言葉わかんのかな?
Raw liver body.
生肝体
Where is the raw liver?
生肝体どこかな?
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I don't know where Akane-chan is.
アカネちゃんどこかわかんないんだ
Yeah.
うん
You look even younger.
なんか、もっと幼く見えるね
Give it a try and try again.
ちょっとやってみて、もう一回
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
I wonder if it will get caught by AI?
AIで引っ掛かんないかな?
this.
これ
He's 15 years old.
15歳ですとか
It's a little hot.
ちょっと暑いもんね
Oh, amazing.
あ、すっごい
Very pale.
めちゃくちゃ色白い
beautiful.
綺麗
As people become older, more and more people like their armpits.
おじさんになってくると脇が好きな人が増えるんで
You've never had your armpits taken so much, right?
脇こんなに取られたことないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Why do you think this person is taking so much money?
なんだこの人こんなに取ってんだろうと思ってる?
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じね
So beautiful.
すっごい綺麗
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗じゃん
18 years old.
18歳
Akane-chan.
アカネちゃん
Yeah.
うん
What is this?
なにこれ
Can you understand even if you murmur?
むぎゅーしてもわかる?
Mugyu.
むぎゅー
Too cute.
可愛すぎ
It's so damn cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛すぎ
Look straight ahead.
正面向いてよ
Facing the front.
正面向いて
Oh, I can't see down.
あ、下が見えない
Can't you see it now?
今から見えないのかな?
Do it, butt forward.
やって、お尻を前に
It's insanely soft.
めちゃめちゃ柔らかい
Oh, what?
あ、なに?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Low pants?
ローパン?
Eh, what do you mean?
え、どういうこと?
What, did you come in low pants?
え、ローパンで来たの?
I came in low pants.
ローパンで来た
It's my first time.
す っごい初めてなんだよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Good, finally, finally.
いいよいいよいいよ
Just do it like this,
ちょっとじゃあこうやってやって、
hey.
ね
If you're talking about this, then just sit back.
これとじゃあちょっと、そう、腰を落として
I sat down and said, oh yeah, yeah.
腰を落として、そうそうそう
She's really wearing no panties.
本当にノーパンだね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
What is that?
それはなに?
Have you forgotten?
忘れてきちゃったの?
Or are you feeling fired up today?
それとも今日気合入れてきたの?
Which one?
どっち?
I've gotten fired up.
気合入れてきた
It's already cute, but it's serious.
もう可愛いんだけどマジで
This is my third time with my uncle.
おじさんと3回目ましてだから
Have you gotten fired up for the third time?
3度目ましてで気合入れてきたの?
yes.
そう
She's a cute girl, even if she looks a little more forward.
可愛い女だな、もうちょっと前向いても
I'll tighten it once.
一回締めてあげるから
I was surprised.
びっくりしたな
I feel like it was the bare minimum I was called for.
呼ばれてた最低限の気がする
That's because I don't know.
わかんないからあれなんだけど
It's okay, it's okay, I'm hiding.
大丈夫、大丈夫、隠れてる
Oh, your butt is also amazing and beautiful.
あ、お尻もすごい、綺麗
Oh, your butt is beautiful too.
あ、お尻も綺麗
A little frilly, fluffy.
ちょっとフリフリして、フリフリ
blue
あ、お
Butt.
尻
Open your butt?
お 尻を開ける?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Not much butt.
お尻あんまり
Ah, I can't see it.
あ、みられない
Oh, it's so soft
あ、すごい柔ら
shellfish.
か い
Amazing, so beautiful.
すごい、めちゃくちゃ綺麗
I can see your butt and pussy.
お尻もマンコン丸見えるよ
It's cute.
かわいいね
I can see it myself.
自分で見えるよ
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だね
This is a little bit of that, so here's a little butt.
これじゃあちょっとあれだから、ここにじゃあちょっとお尻
Do it, do it backwards,
やって、 そのまま後ろにやって、
That's right.
つぱーんってそう
Can you do a piledriver?
まんぐり返しできる?
Can you do a little piledriver?
まんぐり返しちょっとできる?
Does your butt look like it's going to fall off?
お尻落っこっちゃいそう?
It's so beautiful.
めちゃめちゃ綺麗
I haven't used it at all yet.
まだ全然使用してないから
Your nose is tiny too.
鼻もちっちゃいね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'll take some more.
もうちょっと取るよ
Hey Manguri-san, I can't even do teeth.
ちょっとまんぐりさん、歯もできないから、
I guess it's okay to stay like this.
いい気かなこのまま
Put it in.
入れちゃって
It's small here.
ここは狭い
It's a mess, isn't it?
めちゃくちゃしのあるよね
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
The hole from earlier is open.
さっきの穴開いちゃってるよ
I'm sorry, but I opened my uncle's arm.
ごめんね、おじさんの腕開いちゃった
It suits you so well.
めちゃくちゃ似合うよ
That's terrible.
やばいね
A criminal.
犯罪者ね
Are you a criminal?
犯罪者ですか?
That's not true.
違いますね
I feel like I'm a criminal myself.
私、自分で犯罪者かと思うぐらい、
I feel like I'm doing something wrong.
悪いことしちゃってるような感じするんだけど
Because I was told I wasn't wearing a bra.
ノ ーブラって言われたからさ
You said earlier that you were wearing no panties.
ノーパンってさっき言ってたじゃん
I thought I'd like to try wearing no bra or panties.
ノーブラノーパンしてみたいなと思って、
I prepared a costume like this.
こういう衣装を用意しましたけど
Have you ever done something like this?
こんなのしたことある?
Have you ever done gymnastics without a bra?
ノーブラで体操力したことある?
forward.
前
Nowadays, it's not bloomers.
今ってさ、ブルマじゃないでしょ
You've never worn Toburuma, have you?
トーブルマ、履いたことないでしょ
Does it bite?
食い込む?
I feel like I'm saying something, a little bit.
なんか言わしてる感あるな、なんかちょっと
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
Behind or something.
後ろとか
That's a pervert.
変態だね
stand
立
I'm having trouble.
っちゃ ってるよ
Let me check it out.
調べてさせて
Please stand again.
また立ってね
Can you lick it?
舐めれる?
Will it arrive?
届くかな?
I'll do my best and see if it reaches my mouth.
頑張って、口に届くかな
Are you feeling better?
元気になって?
The sperm from earlier also came out.
さっきの精子も出てきて
Are you feeling better?
元気になってる?
How was the second Otenma?
2本目のお天真どうだった?
good.
よかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It came out, it came out.
出てきた出てきた
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It feels so good.
気持ちよさそうにそんなもん
Smile.
笑って
good?
よかった?
I released a lot of sperm though.
いっぱい精子出しちゃったけど
It was fun.
楽しかったね
thank you.
ありがとう
Shall we go eat?
ご飯食べに行く?
I'll buy you lots of sweets next time.
今度お菓子いっぱい買ってあげるね
see you.
またね
Thank you.
ありがとね